daily.social 2018-10-23

# Privacy Policy | Daily.Social

**PRIVACY POLICY**

In this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”), Big Tree Entertainment Private Limited, (“Company”, “Bigtree”, “we”, “us”) describes how we use information about the users of our Websites and Services (“Users”, You”). We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you the procedures and/or policies we follow on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information on the website accessible at “daily.social” (“Website”) along with any and all mobile applications and services such as software, data feeds, email newsletters, associated interactions with you and/or associated services provided to you on, from, or through such Website and mobile applications (“Services”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other data, including, without limitation, data that we collect offline about our customers, data about our employees or data that others collect on websites that are linked to our Website. This Privacy Policy also does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control. We receive information about you from various sources, including your use of the Services generally and/or from third party websites and services. When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. By using any of our Services, you acknowledge that you have reviewed this

Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by terms and conditions regarding use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, do not install, use, or access our Website or our Services.

**1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

Liking, Commenting and Sharing – You may use your account on social networking services (such as Facebook, Twitter and Google) for liking, commenting, sharing in or through our Services. Please note that social network services are operated by third parties and are not controlled by us. We encourage you to check the applicable privacy policy on each social network and adjust your privacy settings.

Creating and Posting Content – Some features of our Services allow users to create and post content in or through the Services including, but not limited to, written comments. Any content which you have publicly posted or published on or through our Services shall be publicly available by default, and your profile information may appear in the Services as the creator thereof. Further, all content submitted by you to the Services may be retained by us indefinitely. We may continue to disclose such content to third parties, as described in this Privacy Policy even if you cease to use our Services. Providing Information – Some part of the Services may require you to voluntarily provide your information such as your name and email address and/or provide your information by logging in to your account in another service (such as Facebook, Twitter and Google). You may further voluntarily provide us with additional information such as your birthday date, gender, location, profile picture and friend list. Such personal information will only be used to operate, maintain, enhance and provide you with our Services.

Protection of your Account – You may never use anothers account without permission. You are solely responsible for the activity that occurs on your account (whether through your email address and/or by logging in through third party social networking sites), and you must keep your account and/or third party account passwords secure. You must notify us immediately of any breach of security or unauthorized use of any of your accounts. We will not be liable for your losses caused by any unauthorized use of any of your accounts.

Other Information – Your profile information (such as nickname, gender and location), information or content you submit, post, like or comment on, and your other activities on the Services will be publicly visible. When you post information or content on or through the Services, we suggest you to think carefully about what you are making public. Contact Information – We may use your contact information such as email address, without further notice, to send you information about our Services, respond to your requests, or facilitate your use of the Services. Cookies – Like many websites, we use cookies and beacons to assist in delivering the Services and to collect usage data for improvement of our Services. Cookies are identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your web browser on your hard drive. Persistent and session cookies are used to identify unique visitors and to provide a customized user experience.

Log Data – Like many other websites and mobile applications, we receive log data when you interact with our Services for delivering our Services and track, customize and improve them. Log data may include information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, kind and version of operating system, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, link click behavior etc.

Third-Party Services – We are not responsible for practices employed by any websites or mobile applications linked to or from our Services. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third-party services. Hence we encourage you to read applicable privacy policy on each website or mobile application that you visit.

Service Providers – We may use various third-party services to provide our Services and to understand the use of our Services. These third parties may have access to your information to the extent it is reasonably necessary.

**2\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

Any information you share such as your profile information (such as nickname, gender and location), information or content you submit, post, like or comment on, and your other activities on the Services will be accessible by other users of the Website and Services. Content that you create through or upload to the Website will by default be public and available to users of the Website and the Services. Similarly, if you comment on any Content (as defined in the [Terms of Use](https://daily.social/terms-of-use/)) on the Website or the Services, your comments will be public and available to users of the Website and the Services.

We may share data about our users or the use of the Website or Services with our advertisers and partners. This means that we may tell our advertisers general information about the characteristics of our user base, but we do not specifically identify a particular user or visitor by name or provide the user’s contact information. We may share your unique device ID and/or your location (based on opt-in location-based services, which rely upon a device’s GPS coordinates) with third parties, including advertisers and partners, or provide reports to such parties about the number of unique users who saw or clicked on their advertisements. We may also share certain information such as cookie data with third-party advertising partners. This information, among other things, allows third-party ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.

We may disclose your information on a confidential basis to non-affiliated service providers we engage to perform services for Bigtree in connection with the Website and our provision of the Services. Information will be shared with such service providers only to the extent reasonably necessary for them to perform such services.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding any personally identifiable data you provide, we may preserve and disclose your information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so in connection with any legal investigation, or by law or regulation, including in response to a court order, subpoena or other legal demand or request.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding any personally identifiable

data/information you provide, we may preserve and disclose your information

if we believe in good faith that it is reasonably necessary to protect the safety

of any person, to address fraud, security or technical issues, to protect

Bigtree’s rights or property, and/or to investigate or assist in preventing any

violation or potential violation of the law, this Privacy Policy, or our Terms of

Use.

We may share some or all of your information in connection with, or during

negotiation of, any merger, financing, acquisition or dissolution, transaction or

proceeding involving sale, transfer, divestiture, or disclosure of all or a portion

of our business or assets. In the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or

receivership, your information may also be transferred as a business asset. If

another company acquires our company, business or assets, that company

will possess the information collected by us and will assume the rights and

obligations regarding your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

(i) Creation Of Anonymous And Aggregated Data

We may create Anonymous Data (i.e., your personal information/data that has

been anonymized by or for Bigtree so that it does not allow a third party to

easily identify a specific individual) and/or Aggregated Data (i.e., your

information/data that has been combined by or for Bigtree into anonymous

groups of users where the groups are large enough to reasonably prevent

individual users from being identified) records from the information/data you

provide by excluding information (such as your name) that makes the data

personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous and Aggregated Data

to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of

our Services and improve Website navigation. We reserve the right, in our

sole discretion, to use Anonymous and/or Aggregated Data for any purpose

and to disclose Anonymous and/or Aggregated Data to third parties for any

purpose.

3\. SECURITY

We take reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information from

loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

But, you should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely

secure or error-free. In particular, messages sent to or from this Website may

not be secure. Please notify us as soon as possible if you suspect that there

is any breach of security.

4\. ADVERTISING

Bigtree displays targeted advertisements. When an advertiser books an ad

placement on the Website, they are given the opportunity to choose their

audience by location, demographics, gender and any other non-personally

identifiable information we receive or collect from you.

By interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that

the advertiser may make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria

used to display the ad. Please note that this Privacy Policy in no way restricts

or limits our collection and use of aggregate information which is data we

collect about your use of our Website or about a group or category of services

or users, from which individual identities or other personally identifiable

information has been removed.

Advertisers may sometimes place their own cookies on your computer in

order to make their ads more effective.

Please remember that any personal information you provide on the linked

pages, ads you click on or other websites is subject to a third party’s privacy

policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such linked websites, ads you

click on or other website, and we are not responsible for the content or privacy

and security practices and policies of these websites or any other websites

that are linked to from our website. We encourage you to learn about their

privacy and security practices and policies before providing them with

personal information.

Also, third party ad networks may serve ads on our Website or provide ads via

our services and/or otherwise place cookies, web beacons or other devices or

technologies on our Platforms (or via our Services) to enable them to

automatically collect non-personal information about you and your visits to our

Website and to other websites, your IP address, your ISP and the browser

you use to visit our Website and other websites. Information collected may be

used, among other things, to analyze data, to deliver content and advertising

on our Website or other websites (including content and advertising that is

targeted to your interests), to determine the popularity of certain content, and

to better understand the usage and visitation of our Website and the other

websites tracked by these third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to,

and we are not responsible for, cookies or clear GIFs in third party ads, and

we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad

services to learn more about their use of cookies and other technologies.

5\. EXCEPTION AND MODIFICATION/DELETION OF INFORMATION

Legal and Other Requirements – Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in

this Privacy Policy, we may disclose your information to a third party if we

believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or

legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or

technical issues; or to protect our rights and property.

6\. PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at our sole discretion

without prior notice and at any time and if we change it materially, we will post

a revised version on this Website. Please check back periodically, and

especially before you provide any personally identifiable information to us. By

continuing to use the Services after changes are made, you agree to be

bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

7\. TERMS OF USE

Note also that your use of our Website and/or Services is subject to our

Terms of Use, which contain disclaimers, limitations of liability, a choice of

Indian law, and consent to the jurisdiction of State and courts in Mumbai and

which is available at DailySocial’s [Terms of use](https://daily.social/terms-of-use/).

8\. CONTACT US

Please feel free to contact us with any comments, questions, complaints or

suggestions you might have regarding the information practices described in

this Privacy Policy. You may send us an e-mail at hello@daily.social.
